<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ashrine</string>
    <string-array name="array_texts">
        <item>Renisha, I hope you\'ve reached someplace goood, and you\'re having a good time. Have a good day/evening/night wherever you are, Take care. :)</item>
        <item>Hey, how is the heat? Think of me, I\'m cool, that should cool your head down :P I hope you\'re having a good time, taking your medicine majjale on time. Take care Renisha. You\'re probably going to be on train whole day aja. But these messages may jumble up on different days, anyways.</item>
        <item>Renisha, it\'s Shakar\'s bla bla time. How are you? Haha, you can\'t reply to that. "Did you know there is something abnormally perfect about your eyes?" Hhahahahahahhahahha :P Hope you are sleeping well, I bet you miss it, but it\'ll be worth it for sure. Take care :)  </item>
        <item>It\'s me again. Take a picture ? Turn that camera on and take a selfie right now, and show it to me later: "This was when I read your text" :D Take care"</item>
        <item>Hello Renisha, hope you\'re eating ramrari,please don\'t be dherai choosy(couldn\'t find a better word sorry) over food hai, i\'m sure you\'re not but still, bhokai chai nabasa</item>
        <item>Renisha, hope you\'re staying safe  and taking care of yourself.Majjale, Majja gara</item>
        <item>Are ooo behna, India kesa hein. Accha hein? Acche se Rehena, tanna khana pina </item>
        <item>Yoooooooooo fulkumari, Nepali birseko chainau ni? Haha, if you see this message before you\'re on the beach, while on the beach please do the Sahi ho Pose :D</item>
        <item> Hmmmmm, Renisha. Hope it\'s not too hot,even if it is, I hope the fan has served it\'s purpose. I guess it\'d be okay to have ONE ice cream cone, haha just one though. I\'m sure you\'ve had one ta already, take care though </item>
        <item> Laylaaa Laylaaaaaa :D Hope you\'re having a good time, make a lot of memorieeees and capture them all</item>
        <item>Renishaaaaa, snap time. Take a snap, aile naiiii. Front camera snappp, no matter how bad :P Take care</item>
        <item> \' Smile Smile Smileeee, smile all day through, Smile Smile Smile and the world is smiling too \'</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>
